

ABOUT ME

I'm an enthusiastic 23-year-old and a recent graduate from Jönköping University, where I specialized in New Media Design. Throughout my academic and professional journey, I have gained practical experience in UI/UX design, graphic design, and frontend development. Working in teams has been particularly enjoyable for me. I have a strong desire to continuously learn and explore new ideas, and I'm always eager to bring creativity to the workplace and projects.

SKILLS

Adobe Creative Cloud
HTML & CSS
JavaScript (Vue.js, React)
PHP & WordPress
Figma
REST API
Link to my portfolio
https://liislepler.github.io/portfolio

LANGUAGES

Estonian - native proficiency
English - full professional proficiency
Swedish - limited proficiency (SFI kurs C)
German - elementary proficiency

CONTACT

liislepler@gmail.com +372 54558338 Gothenburg, Sweden

LIIS LEPLER

EDUCATION

JÖNKÖPING UNIVERSITY (Sweden)

Degree of Bachelor in Informatics (New Media Design)

2020-2023 | Focus on Web Development and Graphic Design

Taken courses such as Web and User Interface Design, Client-side Programming, Graphic Design for New Media, Client-Server Communication, Interaction Design, Motion Graphics, User Research, Applied Web Architecture

PELGULINNA GÜMNAASIUM (Estonia)

Upper-Secondary Education

2016 - 2019 | Graduated in the field of Arts with honors

WORK EXPERIENCE

UI & UX DESIGNER

World Simplified UG

02/2022 - 06/2022 (internship)

- Doing the UI & UX design on Figma for the company's new website platform consisting of views for multiple user types.
- Designing the company's graphical profile using Photoshop, Illustrator, and InDesign.

DESIGN FREELANCING

Book design for print - OT Service 10/2021 - 11/2021

- Doing text and pictures alignment in InDesign for a childrens' book for print.
- Front cover design.

SALES ASSISTENT AND ACTING STORE MANAGER

Nordic Digital AS - Electronics Retail 01/2020 - 08/2020

- Giving professional customer service in the field of technology and photography.
- Organizing the store located in the biggest shopping center in Estonia.

SALES ASSISTENT

Apranga Group - Clothing Retail 08/2019 - 11/2019